card-making-downloads.com 2019-04-04

# Privacy Policy : Instant Card Making Downloads

Privacy Policy For;

Instant Card Making Downloads LTD  
352 – 354 London Road  
Mitcham  
Surrey  
CR4 3ND  
United Kingdom

VAT No.: GB 131 0897 31  
Registered in England and Wales Company Number 7604198.

Web sites that we own;

www.card-making-downloads.com  
www.scrapbookingmad.com  
www.commercial-use-scraps.com  
www.commercial-use-clip-art.com

Instant Card Making Downloads LTD respects your privacy, we are committed to protecting your personal information. We have updated our privacy policy to reflect the changes in data protection law. The new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) will be effective from 25th May 2018. You do not need to take any action, if you would like to know more about this you can read our updated Privacy Policy [**_HERE_**](https://www.card-making-downloads.com/index.php?main_page=page&id=73). Information collected from you will be used solely for the purpose of processing your order and marketing within our business, if you have agreed to receive such correspondence. This information will remain with Instant Card Making Downloads LTD and will not be sold or passed on to third parties.

When you sign up for our news letter your email address will only be used by us to inform you of our updates and special offers and will not be sold or passed on to third parties.

What information we collect from customers;

To ensure a secure ordering process we collect the following information.

Company Name (If you have a company)  
Name,  
Postal Address,  
Telephone Number,  
E-mail Address,  
Credit Card Information (If paying by credit/debit card), PLEASE NOT THAT WE DO NOT STORE YOUR CREDIT CARD INFORMATION.  
IP address.

How We Use This Information;

We use this information to identify our customers, provide customer support and process orders.

We use your e-mail address to notify you of any new items and special offers and important information updates we might have.

If you do not wish to receive e-mails, you may opt out at any time by logging in to your account, click on 'My Account' then under the heading Email Notifications click Subscribe or unsubscribe from newsletters.

We will not provide any personally identifiable information about you to any other person other than a law enforcement or regulatory agency at their request to protect or enforce our rights or the rights of others.

Who We share your information with;

Instant Card Making Downloads LTD respects your privacy, we are committed to protecting your personal information. This information will remain with Instant Card Making Downloads LTD and will not be sold or passed on to third parties.

What information you can chose to receive;

We use your e-mail address to notify you of any new items and special offers and important information updates we might have.

If you do not wish to receive e-mails, you may opt out at any time by logging in to your account, click on 'My Account' then under the heading Email Notifications click Subscribe or unsubscribe from newsletters.

Security procedures in place;

We store your personally identifiable information and payment information in protected environment in encrypted format.

How you can change your account details;

In order to maintain the accuracy of our database, you can check, update or remove your personal details by logging in to your account and updating your details.

Policy Changes;

Instant Card Making Downloads LTD reserve the right to make changes to our policy at any time without any notification. Changes to policy becomes immediately effective upon being posted in this site.
